// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is not a feature of OOP in general definitions?",
    answer: "Duplicate/Redundant data",
    options: [
      "Efficient Code",
      "Code reusability",
      "Modularity",
      "Duplicate/Redundant data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which feature of OOP indicates code reusability?",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    options: [
      "Abstraction",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The feature by which one object can interact with another object is _____________",
    answer: "Message Passing",
    options: [
      "Data Binding",
      "Data transfer",
      "Message Passing",
      "Message reading"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which among the following, for a pure OOP language, is true?",
    answer: "The language must follow all the rules of OOP",
    options: [
      "The language should follow 3 or more features of OOP",
      "The language must follow only 3 features of OOP",
      "The language must follow all the rules of OOP",
      "The language should follow at least 1 feature of OOP"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The copy constructors can be used to ________",
    answer: "Copy an object so that it can be passed to a function",
    options: [
      "Copy an object for type casting",
      "Copy an object so that it can be passed to a function",
      "Copy an object so that it can be passed to a class",
      "Copy an object so that it can be passed to another primitive type variable"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What happens when an object is passed by reference?",
     answer: "Destructor is not called",
     options: [
       "Destructor is not called",
       "Destructor is called at end of function",
       "Destructor is called when called explicitly",
       "Destructor is called when function is out of scope"
     ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which operator can be used to free the memory allocated for an object in C++?",
    answer: "delete",
    options: [
       "Unallocate",
       "Free()",
       "Collect",
       "delete",
     ]
   },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many types of access specifiers are provided in OOP (C++)?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
       "4",
       "2",
       "3",
       "1",
     ]
   },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which among the following can show polymorphism?",
    answer: "Overloading <<",
    options: [
       "Overloading +=",
       "Overloading <<",
       "Overloading &&",
       "Overloading ||",
     ]
   },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which access should a constructor be defined, so that object of the class can be created in any function?",
    answer: "Public",
    options: [
       "Protected",
       "Any access specifier will work",
       "Private",
       "Public",
     ]
   },
   
];